Guide to the Alain Giami collection on sexual practices and attitudes and their health outcomes, circa 1980-2016.
Giami, Alain collection on sexual practices and attitudes and their health outcomes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Alain Giami collection on sexual practices and attitudes and their health outcomes, circa 1980-2016.
7833
Giami, Alain.
14
Research materials, printed materials, publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains faculty research papers as well as documentation (i.e., erotic and pornographic magazines) from sub-Saharan Africa, Brazil, France, Norway, and the United States.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
French socal scientist, director of research at the Institut national de la santé et de la recherche médicale. He works particularly on the use of the condom, the sexuality of disabled people, and the attitudes of medical doctors and nurses.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains faculty research papers as well as documentation (i.e., erotic and pornographic magazines) from sub-Saharan Africa, Brazil, France, Norway, and the United States.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Giami, Alain.
Subjects:
Sexology -- Research.; Sex customs.; Medical personnel -- Attitudes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Sex research conferences, 1984-2011
  - Sexology as a profession in France, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Lecture
  - Lectures, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Articles, 1984, 1991-1992, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Research papers, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sexually transmitted diseases, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Publications
  - STD Dissertation, 1998-10; Miranda, Angelica Espinosa Barbosa (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Research papers, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Les traitments de l'impuissance, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Research papers, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Papers, 1999-11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Contain annotations
  - Conference on social representation, 1995, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AIDS in Europe, 1998-01-12-1998-01-15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Summer institute on sexuality culture and society, 1998-07-12-1998-08-08 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sex conference materials, 2000's (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 5th European Federation of Sexology, 2000-06-29-2000-07-02 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sexualities in transition, 2001-06-12-2001-06-16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - IASR, 27th meeting, Montreal, 2001-07-11-2001-07-14 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Symposium SSRC, Paris, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Euro HIV, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AFSR - sexuality and religion, 2002-02-04-2002-02-05 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - IASR, 2002-06 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - IASR - Hamburg, 2002-06 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 6th European Federation of Sexology and others, 2002-07-05-2002-07-09 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - AIHUS - Bordeaux, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - AIHUS - Montpelier, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ESA - Murcia, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - International Academy of Sex Research (IASR) 26th Annual Meeting, 2000-06-21 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1st International Consultation on Erectile Dysfunction; Handouts, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Socio-Cultural, Educational, and Ethical Aspects of Erectile Dysfunction; Correspondance and Drafts, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Research Papers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Brazilian Handouts, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Academy 98; Scholarly Papers, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - IV Congrès de la Fédération Européene de Sexologie Lisbonne, 1998-09-18 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Portuguese Sexuality Survey, 1998-09-07 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - IASR 25th Annual Meeting Documents, 1999-06-23 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Request for Funds Sidaction, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - IASR 23rd Annual Meeting Documents, 1997-07-23 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - IASR 24th Annual Meeting Documents, 1998-06-03 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - AIDS in Europe; Documents and Notes, 1998-01-08 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Colloque International L'Eugénisme Après 1945, 1997-09-22 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Séminaire; La Santé Publique Au Prisme des Sciences Sociales, 1997-09-11 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - XIV Congrès de la Société d'Andrologie de la Langue Française, 1997-11-27 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 4e Symposium Association Européene de Psychiatrie, 1997-10-17 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1996 Annual Meeting; The Society of Scientific Study of Sexuality, 1996-11-14 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Kingsey Institute Methodology Symposium, 1996-04-26 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - IASR 21st Annual Meeting Documents, 1995-09-20 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Aids in Europe; Research on AIDS, 1998-01-12 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - IASR 22nd Annual Meeting Documents, 1996-06-26 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - XI International Association for the Study of Sexuality, Culture, and Society, 2007-06-27 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Health Psychology Conference, 2008-09-09 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 3es Assises Françaises de Sexologie et de Santé Mentale, 2010-03-21 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Approche Sociologiques de la Médecine Générale, 2006-06-08 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 37e Séminaire de l'AIHUS, 2007-03-29 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 8th Congress of the European Federation of Sexology, 2006-06-04 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 36e Séminaire de Percetionne,ment en Sexologie Clinique, 2006-03-30 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 2es Assises Françaises de Sexologie et de Santé Sexuelle, 2009-03-26 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 9th Congress of the European Federation of Sexology, 2008-04-17 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - IASR 34th Annual Meeting, 2008-07-09 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 2nd Congress of European Federation of Sexology, 1994-06-02 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Formation Psychologique pour Medecins et Soignants, 1989-05-02 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - XXVII Seminaire de Perfectionnement en Sexologie Clinique, 1997-03-13 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - European Crossroads for Sexology, 1996-03-14 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - IASR 20th annual meeting documents, 1994-06-28 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Microbicides, 2002-05-15 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Microbicides, 2002-05-15 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Sexology in Europe, 2003-01 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - IASR 25th annual meeting documents, 1999-08-23 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 3rd Mediterranean Symposium of Andrology, 2004-05-27 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ISCHP 4th international conference, 2005-03-29 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - XXXIe congres de le societe Francoise de sexologie clinique, 2005-10-21 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 28th NACS conference and annual meeting, 2005-09-08 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 35e seminaire de l'aihus, 2005-03-10 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 34e seminaire de l'aihus, 2004-03-18 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Misc. info packets 1 of 2, 2005-2007 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Misc. info packets 2 of 2, 2005-2007 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - International conference, the parmaceutical life cycle, 2009-09-21-2009-09-24 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - AFS, troisieme congres de l'association Francaise de sociologie, 2009-04-14-2009-04-17 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 2es Assises Françaises de Sexologie et de Santé Sexuelle, 2009-03-26-2009-03-29 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - XV congreso latinoamericano de sexologia y educacion sexual, 2010-10-21-2010-10-23 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 4es assises Francaises de sexologie et de sante sexuelle, 2011-03-31-2011-04-03 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - International society for critical health psychology, 2009-07-08-2009-07-11 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 12th congress of the European society for sexual medicine, 2009-11-15-2009-11-18 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Conference material, 2009-2010 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 32nd annual meeting and conference of the Nordic association for clinical sexology, 2010-10-14-2010-10-17 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - International academy of sex research, 36th annual meeting, 2010-07-25-2010-07-28 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Conference material 1 of 2, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Conference material 2 of 2, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Annual meeting, society for the scientific study of sexuality, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Seminarioi avaliacao dos estudos de sexualidade, 1997-07-07-1997-07-08 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Beyond boundaries: sexuality across culture, 1st international conference, 1997-07-29-1997-08-01 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Giami, Undated; FD-578; Floppy disc (Box 15)
  - Kinsey methodology conference, 1996-04; FD-579; Floppy disc (Box 15)
  - Disc double, Undated; FD-580; Floppy disc (Box 15)
  - VIII Reunion de antropologia del mercosur, 2009; CD-3554; CD (Box 15)
  - EFS, 2008; CD-3555; CD (Box 15)
  - Bizarre, Undated; CD-3556; CD (Box 15)
  - Sexualidade humana, Undated; CD-3557; CD (Box 15)
  - Microbicides, conference abstracts, 2002; CD-3558; CD (Box 15)
- Series II. Research files, 1980-2013
  - Prozac related materials, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Prozac related materials, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - HIV related materials, 1990, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Viagra press packet, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Viagra articles and ads, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Viagra articles and ads, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Viagra articles and ads, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Viagra articles and ads, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Viagra information pamphlets, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - ODE Pfizer materials, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - ODE Pfizer materials, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Viagra related articles, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Viagra related materials, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Erectile dysfunction report, 1998-07 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Anti depressant study, 1998-07 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Treatment of impotency and other maladies, 1998-11 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Tigra related materials, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tigra related materials, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Definitions, Date unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Scholarly papers on erectile dysfunction, Date unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Prevalence de l'impussance masculine, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Laboratoires Upjohn
  - Ejaculation rapide, precose ou prematuree, 1998-04-25 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Scholarly papers, psycho-sexology, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Scholarly papers, pharmacological treatments, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous research papers, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Viagra, 1998-07-16 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Durex global sex survey, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Various magazines and newspaper clippings, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Scholarly papers, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous handouts, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Portugal survey: partner relations and risk of HIV infection, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Various German surveys, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Various Swiss surveys, 1987-1992 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - The Norwegian sexual behaviour study, 1987-11-1992-11 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Scotland survey: LAH-AIDS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Various Dutch surveys, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Various Greek surveys, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Finnish sex, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Various Finnish surveys, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Comportement sexuels et reactions au risque du sida en Belgique, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Comportement sexuels et reactions au risque du sida en Belgique, 1993-11-15 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - The national survey of sexual attitues and lifestyles (UK), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - National study of health and sexual behavior, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Enquete nationale VIH (France), 1991-10-1992-03 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Analyse des comportements sexuels en France (ACSF), 1991-09-1992-02 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - ACSF Bruxelles, 1994-06-03 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Various Documents Book of Cross-National Analysis of Sexual Behaviour, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    And HIV Risk in Europe
  - Statistics Book of Cross-National Analysis of Sexual Behaviour, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Brazilian Newsclip and Playboy, 1994-01 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Memoires Andrologie Bicetre, 1996-10-11 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sex Methodologies et Enquetes, 1982-1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - ACSF Enquete Pilote, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clipings France Soir, 1992-12-08 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - ACSF Documents, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - ATP Sexualite et Mode de Vie Questionnaires, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - ACSF Groupe de Travail "Determinants", 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - ACSF Questionnaires, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - ACSF Notes and Documents, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Questions Envoyees a Nathalie Bajos, 1990-02-07 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Enquete INSERM, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Etude sur la Formation des Couples, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - ACSF Formation des Enqueteurs, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - ACSF Questionnaires, 1991-03-20 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - INSERM Questionnaires and Documents, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ACSF Chapitre Theorie "Activite Sexuelle", 1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Sexuality/ACSF Conferences, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Research Notes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Research Data, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Sexuality Questionnaires, 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sexuality Questionnaire 1 of 3, 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sexuality Questionnaire 2 of 3, 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sexuality Questionnaire 3 of 3, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Analysis, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Analysis, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - ACSF Pilot Survey, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - ACSF Pilot Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - ACSF Survey Material, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - ACSF Survey Material, 1990-1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - ACSF Global Press, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Research Press Material, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Les Connaissances, Attitudes, Croyances et Comportements face au SIDA en France, 1992-1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Articles, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Unknown Study Results, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - KAPB Project, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - KAPB Project, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - PWA Relationship, 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - IPSOS Opinion, 1997-12-30 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - French Surveys, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - French Surveys, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Sex Articles 1 of 6, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Sex Articles 2 of 6, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Sex Articles 3 of 6, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Sex Articles 4 of 6, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Sex Articles 5 of 6, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Sex Articles 6 of 6, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Le Choix et les Comportements Affectifs et Sexuels Face au SIDA, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - La grossesses chez les adolescentes en internat, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Prostitution Reports, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - SIDA et Modification des Comportements Sexuels, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - La Seropositivite, 1991-11 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Memoires; Les Formes Notoires de Sexualite Secrete, 1997-09 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Memoires; Prevention du SIDA en Ile de France, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ph.D Thesis; La Prevention du SIDA et les Usage Sociaux de la Jeunesse, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Prospective SIDA 2010, ANRS, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - ANRS Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Les Connaissances, Attitudes, Croyances et Comportements face au SIDA en France ANRS, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - ANRS Meeting Documents, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - VII Conference Internationale sur le SIDA ANRS, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Various ANRS Reports, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Journal du SIDA, 1998-10 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Le Crack de l'Amerique a l'Europe, 1995-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Social and Preventive Medicine, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Informational Pamphlet and Documents on AIDS, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Situation du SIDA de la Population Etrangere Domiciliee en France, 1999-04 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Maitrise; SIDA et Communication Grand Public, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Analyse de Faisabilite d'un Service d'Ecoute Specifique, 1998-11-10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Destine aux Femmes Confrontees a l'Infection du VIH
  - Politics Behind AIDS Policies, 1998-11-18 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Evaluation de la Strategie de Prevention du SIDA en Suisse, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Infection a VIH, Chauffeurs Routiers et Prostituees, 1994-10-30 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Relations Sexuelles et Relation de Confidence, 1990-09 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - La Transmission du VIC Chez les Toxicomanes, 1992-03 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Programme de Lutte Contre le Sida, Plan Triennal de Prevention, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Les Adolescents Faces aux Risques Lies a la Sexualite, 1991-02 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Prostitution, promotion de la sante et prevention du SIDA, 1991-08 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Les homosexuels face au SIDA: Enquete 1995, 1998-03 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Identite profesionnelle, identite de sexe et SIDA, 1995-10 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Surveillance du SIDA, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Papers, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Transcriptase Magazines, 1991-2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - X conference internationale sur le SIDA, 1994-08-11 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Colloque Enjeux des classifications internationales en sante, 1996-06-06 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Swiss HIV Prevention Study, 1994-06-08 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Various Research Papers, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - HIV Questionnaires, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Analyse des comportements sexuels en France (ACSF), 1994-11 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Programme d'actions de prevention de l'infection du VIH/SIDA, 2001-12 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Surveillance du SIDA RNSP, 1995-06-30 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Le travail sexuel, la consommation des drogues et le HIV, 1993-09 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - MRC AIDS Behavioural Forum, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Descriptions des pratiques sexuelles des patients VIH, Suivis dans la cohorte PRIMO, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Annual Conference of the Nordisk Forening for Klinisk Sexologi, 1995-10-01 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - ANRS Journee d'animation de la recherche, dynamique de l'epidemie de SIDA, 2002-01-21 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Les Connaissances, attitudes, croyances et comportements face au VIH/SIDA en France, 1992-2001 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Rapport Intermediaire; Les Connaissances…, 2001-10-15 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    Attitudes, croyances et comportements face au VIH/SIDA en France
  - ANRS Appel d'offres 1993, 1992-06-23 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - ANRS Appel d'offres 1993, 1994-10 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Cross National Analyses of Sexual Behaviour and Attitudes Towards HIV/AIDS Risk in Europe, 1994-12-16 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Heroine, SIDA, Prison, 1996-03 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Ph.D Thesis; Transmission heterosexuelle du VIH-1, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Memoire; Les malades de la maison royale de Charenton, 1992-09 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Memoire; Les usages sociaux du film pornographique gai, 2008-09 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Memoire; Les sex-shops a Paris, 2005-09 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Sterilisation; Manuscripts, Documents, Clipings, 1999-01 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Sterilisation generale, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Sterilisation, conference reforme sexuelle, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Sterilisation, handicapes mentaux 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Sterilisation, handicapes mentaux 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Handicap film avec Colette Piquet, 1984-04-1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Handicap film entretiens avec Christophe, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - APEAI du BITERROIS Notes, 1997-02 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - UNAPEI. Sex. SIDA, Handicap 1 of 3, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - UNAPEI. Sex. SIDA, Handicap 2 of 3, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - UNAPEI. Sex. SIDA, Handicap 3 of 3, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Hardy, reference aux entretiens, Date unknown (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Analyse item par item, Date unknown (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Memoire; l'obligation legale d'un examen prenuptial en France, Date unknown (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Handicap Notes and Research Papers, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - XVI Colloque AIR Sexualite, procreation des personnes handicapees, 1997-10-25 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - FFSM Colloque bioethique et sante mentale, 2002-10-28 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Les intercommissions 1995-1999, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - ADAPEI Projet d'un programme d'action, 1992-11 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Colloque St. Brieuc, 1992-06-12 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Colloque nationale handicap et sante mentale, 1992-06 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Intervention Sex/H, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Representations Sex/H Exposes, 1993-05-15 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Sexualite et sterilisation des incapables, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers de presse "Affaire du Coral", 1982-11-25 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondences Gilles Pinault, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - La sexualite des personnes handicapees mentales en institution, 1998-01 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - La deficience intellectuelle face a la prevention du VIH, 1996-12-10 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Research Papers Handicap et Sterilisation, Notes, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Andre Dupras, 1982-03-10 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Sexualite, Institutions, Handicaps, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - CRE Dijon, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Seminaire sexualite et sante, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Articles Alain Giami, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 51e Rencontre prevention des risques sexuels et handicap, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Haute ecole Fribourgeoise du travail social, documents, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Nice Preparation documents sexualite, institutions, handicaps, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - La vie affective et sexuelle de la personne handicapee, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Journee de formation du CREAHI, Documents, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Formation-Action des personnes ressources en education a la sexualite, 2001-12-31 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - International Journal of Public Health, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Handicap Deficiencies and Sexuality Research Bibliography, 2001-08 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Relations of Handicap People Living. Notes, 2003-12-2004-01 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - UNESCO Sexual Health and Human Rights, 2013-04-21 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - The Prevention of HIV Transmission Between Psychiatric Patients, 2000-06-2001-01 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Personne handicapee, vie affective et sexuelle, quelle place dans les institutions?, 2011-2013 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Environnements a risque et promotion de la sante sexuelle, 2004-11 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Les etablissements de consommation sexuelle
  - Echangistes related material, 2001-2004 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Echangistes related material, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - French Ministry of Health Reports, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Sexualite et institution, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Organisation de la vie quotidienne, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Education sexuelle, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Gestion de la procreation, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Attitude par rapport au VIH, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Prevention VIH/SIDA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Seropositivite en intitution, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - SIDA Maladie, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Responsabilite Ethique, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Depistage du VIH, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fiches identification uniquement, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Autres aspects abordes par la personne interviewee, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)